BRANDON LAMBRECHT

KALISPELL, MT | 406-281-2139 | BRANDONJLAMBRECHT@GMAIL.COM | LINKED IN URL

BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP EXPERT / DIGITAL MARKETING ENTHUSIAST

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Relationship oriented leader with 6 years experience in account management within finance, retail, and health/wellness industries. Skilled in building trustworthy relationships and identifying areas of opportunity for continuous business growth. Strong skill set in managing creative teams and leading strategy to enable organization-wide success.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- CRM Management
- Social Media Management
 Workflow Delegation

- Market Analysis
- Sales Prospecting

- Brand Development
 Marketing Strategy
 Market Analysis
 Working Delegation
 Account Management
 Remote Adaptability
 Contract Negotiation
 - Contract Negotiation
- Coaching & Training
- ❖ Strategic Planning
- KPI Setting and TrackingExecutive Collaboration
- Performance Management

CAREER HIGHLIGHTS

Account Management: Managed 200+ plus accounts focusing on relationship building and customer experience resulting in growth of business accounts

Brand Development: Grew fitness brand to a top 5 revenue producer in the nation under 12 months of launch by leveraging digital channels and providing high level coaching

Industry Flexibility: 6 years adapting to new lines of business and product categories while maintaining impact on sales success

EXPERIENCE

BUSINESS FINANCE MANAGER

JESCO MARINE & POWER SPORTS | KALISPELL, MT | OCT 2022 - PRESENT

- Assist in strategic decision making to manage 5-10 million in inventory, plan for brand growth, and forecast supply and demand
- Collaborate on marketing strategies, KPI's, campaigns, and event planning to align with business goals.
- Finalize on all contracts to ensure gross profit target of 10-30% is achieved
- Optimize CRM to identify the best fit in the marketing funnel during customer journey

RELATIONSHIP DEVELOPMENT & SUPPORT

BMO HARRIS BANK | MILWAUKEE, WI | MAR 2019- JUNE 2022

- Administered business relationships for internal and external divisions to foster new and current relationships
- Individually managed, tracked, and maintained 200+ customer accounts focusing on cost saving strategies to increase bottom line
- Led, trained, and managed the missing collateral department to identify and recover missing data for new and current contracts.
- Consistently hit monthly metrics, 95% efficiency, 100% work quality, and customer satisfaction.

EXPERT COACH/BRAND AMBASSADOR

SOLIDCORE | MILWAUKEE, WI | DEC 2020 - JUNE 2022

- Cultivated brand awareness in a competitive Pilates market by leveraging social channels, developing customer and business relationships.
- Built personal brand as professional, educated, and welcoming expert coach through both digital and in-person platforms.
- Collaborated with the team to grow a new studio into a top 5 revenue performer in the nation.
- Positioned myself as a specialized pro coach with innovative programming, knowledge in specialty classes, and priority in customer experience.

MEMBER EXPERIENCE MANAGER

ANYTIME FITNESS | BILLINGS, MT | OCT 2017- MAR 2019

- Led, taught, and developed a successful team to grow quarterly in revenue by 15%.
- Scheduled and coordinated meetings, appointments, and training sessions for over 80 clients.
- Intuitive content creator for all social campaigns.
- Followed through on all critical inter-departmental escalations to increase member retention rates.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN MARKETING, MONTANA STATE UNIVERSITY | BOZEMAN, MT |

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN MARKETING, UNIVERSITY OF EXETER | EXETER, UK |

CERTIFICATIONS

- Google Ad Manager
- Google Analytics 4
- Hubspot CRM